mutualart.com 2010-04-24

# MutualArt.com - PrivacyPolicy

Privacy Policy 

Thank you for visiting www.MutualArt.com, a MutualArt Holding (“MutualArt”) website (the “Site”). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. 

Capitalized terms used and not otherwise defined in this document shall have the meanings set forth in the MutualArt.com Terms of Use Agreement. 

Information Collection and Use by MutualArt.com

MutualArt.com collects user submitted information such as [name, email address] to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the MutualArt.com service. MutualArt.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: art collecting preferences including artists, genres, and cities of interest as well as such other demographic, geographic and psychographic information for internal use by MutualArt.com or its service providers in connection with the MutualArt.com Services. 

However, we will not send unsolicited messages to Users of our Site who indicate that they do not wish to receive such messages. MutualArt.com may use the information you provide about yourself and specifically your art collecting preferences to deliver content including but not limited to news and events that we believe may be of interest to you, while using MutualArt.com. Additionally, MutualArt.com will use the same information you provide about yourself to deliver content including news and events that we believe may be of interest to you and deliver such information via e-mail based on your stated e-mail preferences. 

MutualArt.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the Site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

Certain User profile information including Members' first name is displayed to a user and viewable once they have logged into the application. Other MutualArt.com users cannot view the status of who has logged into the application nor is there a platform to communicate between logged in members (e.g. chat, messaging). Email addresses are used for the purposes of allowing direct communications between MutualArt.com and users, subject to the requests of such users, and to send notifications related to the service User's full name and email address will no be shared or displayed to other Users. The sole exception is a User may have the opportunity to request price quotations for art services that are of interest to them including but not limited to lighting, insurance, shipping and such other services. Such Users upon completion of a form in which they directly completed – can choose to have their information shared with the vendors who will fulfill the services of interest and interact with the User. 

Information collected through the MutualArt Service may be stored and processed in any countries in which we or our service providers maintain facilities. You therefore understand and consent that your information may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. 

Sharing and Disclosure of Information MutualArt.com Collects

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, MutualArt will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by MutualArt.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the MutualArt.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. MutualArt reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of MutualArt or any of its assets. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

Use of Cookies

MutualArt.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from MutualArt.com in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that MutualArt allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the MutualArt Privacy Policy. 

Links 

MutualArt.com contains links to sites. MutualArt.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on MutualArt.com. 

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information 

MutualArt.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing the user profile In the My Account section that is prominently available on all pages of the application. 

Email Choice/Opt-out 

We may use a User's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications or change the frequency of such communications may choose to do so from within the preferences area of the My Account section. Users who do not wish to receive MutualArt.com newsletters may choose not to by de-selecting either the “Daily” or “Weekly” options that are listed on the Newsletter Preference. For clarification, a user is not required to have either option selected. All notification emails and MutualArt.com newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future. 

Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to Users by MutualArt.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by MutualArt.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Security

MutualArt.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. MutualArt.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. Please do not transmit any private or confidential information to us by email or through this Site. We cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. 

For any additional information about the security measures we use on MutualArt.com, please contact us at info@MutualArt.com 

Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. 

Contacting the Web Site

MutualArt.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at info@MutualArt.com   

Effective: June 01, 2009
